Muhammad Zaryab Rafique

Programmer

I'm a person who has the passion to learn new technology that the market demands and needs of the future. Impossible aims can achieve with teamwork and hard work. I am passionate to add value to an organization's work through my expertise.



| 🔀 mu | hammac | Izarya | brafic | que@gmai | l.com |
|------|--------|--------|--------|----------|-------|
|------|--------|--------|--------|----------|-------|

Sahiwal, Pakistan

mzaryabrafique.live

S zaryabpersonal

+92 3347860477

19 June, 1998

linkedin.com/in/zaryab-programmer

github.com/Zaryab-Programmer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Android Developer

Sruplex

02/2021 - Present Remote | Lahore, Pakistan

Tasks

• Build greenfield mobile applications. Develop features and fix bugs

Blockchain Developer & Solidity - Smart Contracts Fiverr & Upwork

02/2021 - Present Freelancing

Tasks

Build DApps, write smart contracts, Web3 integration, testnet, infura.

Android Developer (Team Lead & Trainer) **COMSATS Software House**

Part Time | Sahiwal, Pakistan

06/2019 - 06/2021

 Train the young students in android development. Build android apps for the software house.

Core Member

Developers Student Clubs - Google Developers

Volunteer | Sahiwal, Pakistan

Tasks

- Making projects and deliver them to the DSC Team lead.
- Organizing events and preparing the material

React Native Intern

Dynamic Logix - Software House

05/2020 - 06/2020

Internship | Sahiwal, Pakistan

Tasks

• Building different features for current apps of software house.

Web Designing Intern

Uni Web Solutions

Internship | Sahiwal, Pakistan

8th Semester | 3.02 CGPA

• Design front-end in Adobe Photoshop and convert into website.

EDUCATION

07/2017 - 10/2017

Bachelor of Science in Computer Sciences BS(CS) COMSATS University Islamabad (CUI), Sahiwal Campus

02/2018 - 02/2022 Final Year Project

Final Year Project on Blockchain

SKILLS



PROJECTS

Blockchain Land Records System - FYP

- The Blockchain-based Land Records System is a DApp that the government act as admin can register land, view tax, update the land market value.
- Citizens can mark land to sale, view owned lands, search lands to buy, manage requests.

Decentralized Application Authentication

This project provides the authentication in Decentralized Application on Ethereum Blockchain.

OnMovies Android App (Lived at Play Store)

OnMovies App provides entertainment, user can watch movies, build on Java (Android)

Milk Record App

Milk Record System App helps the milk seller to keep the record of each customer, manage records.

Food Delivery Android App & ASP.Net MVC

 Food Delivery web app developed on ASP.Net MVC and Food Delivery App developed on Android (Java)

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency